"Previously on The Mentalist..."
- Will you come with me to D.C.?
- I wanna say yes. It's just...
Take your time.
There's no deadline.
- Are you going with him?
- To be honest, sir, I don't know.
- What does Jane have to say about this?
- I'm sure he's fine with it.
I need emergency medical assistance
at 812 Ashcroft.
- Bow and arrow.
- What does that mean, "bow and arrow"?
"How long
were you held captive for?"
"I couldn't tell."
"I never saw the sunlight.
Two days, maybe."
- "And you never saw your captor?"
- "No."
My sister's Amy Welker.
She's 16.
You have to find her.
- She was abducted with you?
- Yes.
Her sister was there.
There are more girls.
Forensics is at the safe house now.
They found DNA from 20 different people
on those water bottles.
"And thanks to you,
we shut down a trafficking ring."
- You didn't find my sister?
- No, but we're still looking.
There was another truck. Your sister
may have been on that.
He was just waiting there
all the time?
Yeah. He just makes a point
to be there for me.
- You really like this guy, huh?
- He got a promotion in D.C.
and he asked me to go with him
so we can be together.
"Yeah."
Thank you.
You shopping for real estate?
The bureau is paying for Marcus
to relocate to D.C.
I'm helping him find a place.
- Have you decided?
- Decided what?
Whether or not
you're gonna go with him.
No. Not yet.
Well, I hope you stay.
- You do?
- Yeah, I think you'll be bored in D.C.
That's why I should stay,
to avoid boredom?
- What's worse than boredom?
- Patrick Jane?
- You are Patrick Jane?
- Yeah, when it suits me.
I've got a warrant for your arrest.
Cuff him.
Hold on.
What's going on?
The Attorney General has found
your coworker in contempt of court
for ignoring a federal subpoena.
- Teresa Lisbon?
- Yeah, that's me.
You've been subpoenaed to appear
before a federal grand jury in Dallas.
- What's happening here?
- Well, hold on a minute.
- Are you Kim Fischer?
- Yes.
You've been subpoenaed to appear
before a federal grand jury, as well.
- Let's go.
- Uh, probably best not to ignore those.
"Two years ago, an arrest warrant
was issued for Patrick Jane"
in connection to the murder
of Thomas McAllister
the serial killer
known as Red John.
Is it true you were part
of an international FBI manhunt
- to bring Patrick Jane to justice?
- That's accurate.
And yet now, you work for a unit
of the FBI that employs him.
I am a part of that unit, yes.
The FBI conducts
a two-year manhunt
finds its suspect, and brings him back
but instead of a trial by his peers
he is given a government job
with benefits.
- Why?
- We made a deal with him.
- What were the terms of that deal?
- I don't know.
He was already a part
of the team when I was hired.
Mr. Jane is required to assist us
in cases
in exchange for immunity
from prosecution.
You worked very closely
with Mr. Jane in California.
Does he confide in you?
You close?
You could say that.
Did he tell you
he killed Thomas McAllister?
Not specifically, no.
Did he tell you
he killed Thomas McAllister?
I plead the fifth.
Did he tell you where he was on the day
McAllister was murdered?
I plead the fifth.
Agent Lisbon
are you besmirching your badge
and refusing to answer to protect yourself
or to protect Patrick Jane?
Go to hell.
This is where we found Daniela,
the second trafficking victim.
They separated her
from the rest of the group.
- Any idea why yet?
- No.
The others were being held
inside the house.
It isn't much better.
Now, the girls were abducted
from across the western United States
and transported here by truck.
We believe the traffickers used this house
as a way station of sorts.
It's hard to believe 30 women
were crammed in here.
Took two days to process...
A lotta hair and fibers floating around.
Yeah, I'll bet. Hey.
Can we get some light in here?
We're still looking for the second truck
full of victims
but I think
it's south of the border by now.
What about the truckload
that we did find?
Those girls provide
any useful information?
All they could tell us
about was Jesse.
The dead man who lured them
with the modeling scam.
- Ringleaders remain a mystery.
- Okay.
Well, what about the girl that died?
She was trying to tell Jane something
about a bow and arrow.
We don't know
what that means yet.
I'm hoping for more answers
once we analyze all the evidence.
Okay.
Well, you finish up here
- and I'll see you back at headquarters.
- All right.
- We need to talk.
- In my office. What's going on?
Lisbon and I just got back
from the grand jury hearing in Dallas.
They're trying to indict Jane
for murder.
- Thomas McAllister.
- They asked us point-blank
whether or not Jane had ever
confessed to killing him.
And what did you say to them?
- What are you doing here?
- Uh, I'm out on "bail".
- W-what does "bail" mean?
- It was a con.
Uh, technically the term is "sting".
- Operation jury-scam.
- You're kidding, right?
I am very sorry for the deception
but to maintain authenticity,
we couldn't inform you
until after you sat with the jury.
Our target for the sting
is this man...
John Acardo.
He's a young mob boss.
He owns the illegal
sports-betting market in Dallas.
You guys didn't answer my question.
Did anyone narc on me?
How does indicting Jane
nail Acardo?
This... is Elijah Macy.
He created a sports-betting website
that was cutting into Acardo's profits.
Now, we think that Acardo
had him killed five weeks ago.
What's the evidence?
Well, it's circumstantial
but more than enough to indict.
And then, surprise, surprise the grand
jury voted not to prosecute last week.
You think Acardo got to them.
All they'd have to do
is sway two or three jurors.
And that's what the Attorney General
thinks happened.
Now he's asking for our help.
Fortunately, the same jurors
are impaneled for another month.
And, under the pretense
of a murder investigation
I will face them and determine
which ones were bribed.
Or intimidated.
I can't believe you got a prosecutor
to take part in the con.
It's not a con. It's a sting.
Sting.
The prosecutor doesn't know
that this is not real.
The Attorney General does.
- This is the last of it.
- Thanks.
Is everyone out?
Locking up now.
FBI!
Daniela.
- How'd you get in here?
- The window.
- They released you from the hospital?
- I released myself.
- This is an active crime scene.
- I'm looking for my sister.
We're doing everything we can
to find Amy.
But you haven't found her,
have you?
Daniela, why'd you come back here?
You told us you didn't know
if Amy was even at this house.
I didn't...
but I do now.
This is her tag.
She left it everywhere.
She was here.
Hey. Look at me.
We're gonna find her.
It is none of your business
what I told the jury.
- I did what I had to do.
- What about you, Lisbon?
You snitch on me, huh?
Be honest.
You wanna know what I said,
read the transcripts.
Hey. What did I do?
You shoulda told me this whole
courtroom charade was a charade.
Since when am I a target
of one of your cons?
It wasn't a con.
I don't care.
You shoulda told me.
I thought that you...
You know what?
Forget about it.
Operation jury-scam,
it was Abbott's idea.
He ordered me
not to tell anyone.
Oh, you picked a great time
to start following orders.
- Well, I-I have to do...
- Am I interrupting?
No, it's perfect timing.
I am more than ready for lunch.
I heard about your grand jury.
I'm pulling for you.
I think you did what any good father
and husband would do.
Yes, Jane has all of our sympathies.
Let's go.
How long are you gonna let that go?
What?
Well, you know he's gonna take her
to Washington, right?
Listen, she'll do
what she wants to do.
You know, I've collared
lots of con men over the years
best in the business.
You know what led
to their downfall ultimately?
Yeah. They start believing
their own con.
That's not gonna happen.
There is no con here.
- No?
- No.
All right, then.
Mr. Jane, you understand
you're under a waiver of immunity.
- Yes, ma'am.
- What does that mean to you?
Uh, it means that anything I say
may be held against me.
Very good.
In a moment,
I'll open the floor up to you
so you can provide
a narrative of events
to explain what you were doing
and where you were
on the date and time
of Thomas McAllister's murder.
Objection. You said murder.
Thomas McAllister may have shot
and strangled himself.
There are no objections here, Mr. Jane.
No judge, just a friendly inquiry.
But I take your point.
Do you recall the day
of McAllister's death?
I do, big day.
I had been chasing the man
for eight years.
Any of you know what it's like
to be driven by a moral imperative?
You do.
And you. And you do.
You all have strong jaw muscles.
It's a sign of strength and character.
You, I'm not so sure.
Your eyes are a tad close to each other.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'm establishing
a narrative of events, as you asked.
- So stick to the narrative.
- Narrative, yes, I do love a story.
As do you. You read a great deal
of fiction, don't you?
- Romantic novels.
- That's right.
Yes, an illicit engagement
wouldn't scare you, would it?
Where are you going with this?
I'm trying to tell my story,
if you'll just let me.
- You haven't even started it.
- Well, they seem engaged.
All of them except this gentleman here
who's preoccupied by his new jacket.
That's a little vain and childish,
don't you think?
This is serious business.
Pay attention.
- I'm sorry. I was just trying to...
- Sir, you will not indulge him.
Well, he's happy to indulge himself.
T-that should definitely
be on the record.
Mr. Jane, this is not a forum
for you to chat with the jurors.
- Well, it should be.
- Mr. Jane.
They just seem like good,
honest, friendly people
all of them except that gentleman
on the end there.
You know, you really should
mend things with your son.
All this anger, this bitterness,
this resentment that you're bottling
- it's ruining both your lives.
- Stop now.
You do not dictate the agenda here.
- Who does?
- I do.
This is my courtroom,
and it runs the way I say.
Is that clear?
It is now. Thank you.
- Lydia Faulk?
- Socialized narcissist.
There is no one in that courtroom
keeping her in check.
John Acardo didn't pay off jurors
to avoid prosecution.
He just paid off the prosecutor.
Well, theoretically
a prosecutor could throw an investigation
especially one with circumstantial evidence.
I'll obtain the transcript.
Faulk's too smart to exclude evidence.
It would be in the way
she presented the case.
Halfheartedly, lacking confidence.
jury would see defeat
in her eyes and vote accordingly.
- So, what do you propose?
- A new strategy.
We need to prove that John Acardo
is guilty of murder ourselves.
Jane believes that Acardo
didn't get to the jury.
He got to Faulk, the prosecutor.
- So now we have two targets.
- That's right.
And to take 'em down,
we're gonna have to find proof
that Acardo was behind
the Elijah Macy shooting.
What evidence do we have?
Earlier this year,
one of Acardo's men was arrested
turned state's evidence for immunity
from a drug charge.
He also testified that his boss
order the hit on Macy.
Multiple witnesses heard Acardo
threaten to have Macy killed
if he didn't shut down
his sports-betting website.
But we don't have any physical evidence.
Not yet. But that's what
we're gonna have to find.
Well, according to the transcript
Acardo claims he was at a place
called Il Tavolo Bianco
the night of the murder.
That's his favorite restaurant,
obviously his alibi.
Yeah, but he drones on and on about it
after it was already in the record.
He keeps talking about the restaurant
because he's hiding evidence of his guilt.
You sound like Jane.
Well, you spend enough time
with someone...
Lisbon, why don't you check out
this Il Tavolo Bianco?
And take Jane with you.
You two have a nice dinner on the FBI.
Yeah, sure.
Hey. How are you?
All they've got me doing
is staring at photos of sex traffickers.
I need a shower.
Here you go.
- You're right-handed.
- Uh, yes.
So, that heart on your hand,
y-you didn't draw that?
Uh, no. They did.
Yeah, we don't know what that means.
None of the other girls
we rescued had that mark.
- Guess I'm special.
- Jane.
Excuse me.
I was looking over your interview
with Agent Lisbon.
You mentioned blood tests.
When Amy and I went to our first modeling
gig, the nurse took our blood.
They said we couldn't enter Europe
without a blood test.
They lied.
I'm thinking that mark
has something to do with your blood test.
- Like how?
- We'll find out.
You keep saying that, but nothing happens.
Just keep looking over
those photos, okay?
It's not your fault.
It's all my fault.
I talked Amy into this.
Hey, boss.
- Any breaks in the case?
- Maybe.
They took a sample of blood from all
the trafficking victims, including Daniela.
Well, that's hardly standard procedure
for traffickers.
- Why do you think they needed the blood?
- I don't know yet
but I just went through
all the evidence from the house.
I found these inside a first aid kit...
blood-test equipment.
According to the Q.R. codes
they were supplied by a Dallas company.
Rutherford Medical Supply.
Well, their purchase records
can help find our traffickers.
Good work.
Hey, Cho.
I know you're working with Daniela on this
but try not to get her hopes up.
The longer this stretches on the less likely
we'll be able to find her sister.
It's nice.
A little dark.
I am Aurelio.
- May I hang your coat?
- Yes. Thank you.
This way, please.
I have just the table
for your... special evening.
- Oh, it's just dinner.
- Nonsense.
Every night with this one
is, uh, an occasion, yes?
Can't deny that.
Good. Settle in.
I'll be right back.
I owe you an apology
about the grand jury thing.
I overreacted.
You're just doing what Abbott told you to.
Oh.
Did Marcus help you decide that?
As a matter of fact...
Right. Well, Marcus is wrong.
I should've told you
and you were right to be cross with me.
I pled the fifth, by the way,
in the grand jury room.
Figured as much.
You always know what I'm gonna do, huh?
- Mostly.
- One of these days, I might surprise you.
Please don't. I love that you're predictable.
Just what a girl wants to hear.
What does a girl wanna hear?
I wish I knew.
Your wine menu.
- Thank you.
- If I may...
we just imported a beautiful
Brunello di Montalcino.
Well, uh, what do the mobsters drink?
Yeah, the... the guidebook said that
real-life mobsters used to favor eating here.
Yes. My father once
served Joseph Civello.
Joseph Campisi
all the old Dallas mob families.
They came here
for a taste of the old country.
They used to say, "The veal is good
but the goodfellas... they're bad."
What about now?
Well, fortunately, there are no active
crime families left in Dallas.
Well, isn't there that guy?
What's his name?
The up-and-coming guy
John, uh, Acardo.
He's, uh...
does he ever eat here?
I wouldn't know anything about that.
I'll bring your server.
Thank you.
- It's Italian.
- You're good.
- What do you think?
- I think I'd like to take a look
at the evidence from the original case.
And then I was thinking
about the Brunello di Montalcino.
- That did sound good.
- 130 bucks a bottle.
- Abbott's paying. Let's get it.
- Bingo.
This is all the physical evidence
from the Elijah Macy murder scene.
I sorted it by order of relevance with
this end of the table being most relevant.
What do you consider relevant?
Any object that can yield
trace evidence of the shooter.
If we ID the triggerman, we can
cut a deal with him to finger Acardo.
Yeah, uh, trace evidence
that's the fibers and the hairs
and the gooey stuff, yeah?
That's an oversimplification, but, yes.
In the last year alone,
there are 17 new methods
- for extracting DNA evidence from...
- Yeah, we know that there's a lotta ways
- to find out what we need, right, Wylie?
- Yeah.
So, uh, there's the federal way,
with the trace evidence
and then there's a more interesting way.
Let's go with the more interesting way.
Tell me, hmm?
If I were to ask you what is the most random
item on this table, what would you say?
This. An overcoat.
It was found 200 feet
from the crime scene.
There were no trace elements
found on it.
The detectives weren't even sure
it was connected to the crime scene.
What was the weather like
the day of the murder?
- Pretty warm, if I'm not mistaken.
- Holes. Hmm.
Interesting. You see that, Wylie?
Okay, so, if this didn't belong
to the victim
you have just solved the case.
- I did?
- Well done.
Find out if it belonged to the victim or not.
Okay...
- Mrs. Macy?
- Yes?
Special Agent Fischer, FBI.
I apologize for the intrusion.
I need your help.
It's about your son.
- Um... come on in.
- Thank you.
When you raise a son alone
you don't stop and think about, well...
Anything, really.
You're just trying to keep up.
It wasn't until Elijah was, uh...
taken away that I realized how woven he was
into the fabric of my entire life.
Tell me about him.
Elijah was such an inquisitive child
loved building things
taught himself to code when he was 12.
I understand he started his internet
company while he was still in college.
That's right, junior year.
He was Plan II up at U.T.
and I thought, "Oh, no.
He's just never gonna have the time."
But he was so excited
to launch that website.
In six months...
paid off my house with the profits.
Graduated with honors, too.
Special kid.
Yeah.
If you'll allow me just one more question.
Was this Elijah's Coat?
According to his mother,
Elijah was allergic to wool
and that coat is 100% wool
so it didn't belong to the victim.
I was hoping you would say that.
Well, I know how John Acardo
ordered the hit
and, more importantly,
I know how to prove it.
- How?
- It's easy.
I just need to make
Acardo put a hit out on me.
Acardo, 11 o'clock.
You really think you can get him
to take out a hit on you in one night?
Usually, only people who know you
wanna kill you.
It's just a matter of figuring out
which buttons to push.
A man like Acardo, you know,
he, uh, has a fierce need for control
fancies himself the lord
of all he surveys.
Elijah Macy cuts into his profits
he responds by eliminating
the competition.
A grand jury tries to indict him,
he buys the outcome.
All I need to do is to take something
that belongs to him.
Like what?
What about her?
Good luck with that.
I'll be at the bar.
- Oh! Oh, God.
- I am so sorry.
- Please excuse me.
- No problem. No problem.
It's your arms. They're so sparkly.
Oh, my God.
You noticed my glitter lotion?
Yeah. Oh, look. It's on me, too.
At least somebody did.
Wait, check it out in the light.
- That is fantastic.
- Yeah, it's so shiny.
- Oh, no.
- What is it? What's wrong?
- What is it?
- Um... My... my bracelet.
What does it look like?
Let me help you find it.
- Let me find it.
- It-it's a diamond tennis bracelet.
It's from my fiancé.
- Your fiancé bought you this?
- Yes.
- Thank you! Thank you!
- No, that's fine.
- Thank you.
- Here, look.
I mean, no offense
but I can't say much for his taste.
I would put nothing more than Cartier
on your wrist around your neck
or dangling from here.
- You're so sweet.
- I'm Patrick.
Brandy.
What kinda scotch you got?
Oh, look.
Casablanca is on.
Here's looking at you, kid.
You know Bogart made that line up?
It wasn't in the script.
I've never seen Casablanca.
- What? Are you serious?
- I'm not really into old movies.
This is not an old movie.
This is a classic.
You've gotta watch this.
- You're gonna love it.
- Okay, let's watch it.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm just tired.
Well, Teresa...
I may not be able to read minds
like Jane
but even I can tell
when something's going on.
Jane can't read minds.
It's hard to explain.
You know, it doesn't matter.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
- Not really, no.
I just wanted to say that I know
moving to D.C. is a big thing
and... it might raise issues you don't feel
totally comfortable talking to me about.
But I just want you to know it's okay.
I mean, you go through
whatever process you need to, just...
let me know when you make a decision.
I'll be here.
Thank you.
Let's watch Casablanca, huh?
What is it about, anyway?
Well, various things
but basically it's a love story
about a woman who has to choose
between two men.
There's also a baseball game on.
- That sounds better.
- Yeah, let's do that.
Hey, boss, check this guy out.
- Brandy.
- Dance card's full for the night, friend.
This can go one of two ways.
You can take your hands off her body
or I can cut 'em off.
You must be the fiancé.
Let me tell you something, pal.
You are marrying a wonderful dancer.
It's okay, baby. Nothing to worry about.
Look.
- He found my bracelet.
- Found the bracelet.
- Oh, did he?
- Uh-huh.
- What did you say your name was?
- Uh, this is Patrick.
Jane. Patrick Jane.
Well, Patrick, I think it's time for you
to say good night.
- On your way.
- Oh, no, not yet.
This, this may be my last night
of freedom.
I'm being indicted for murder
and I was hoping to go out big, you know?
Finest champagne, finest woman.
Brandy's spending the night with me.
I hope you don't mind.
- Oh, he's just joking, Johnny.
- Oh, no, I'm not.
And I'm gonna take you places
that you've never been.
And when you get back
you can tell Johnny all about it.
That'll be my wedding gift
to the two of you.
I think our friend Patrick here
has had a little too much to drink.
- Why don't you escort him out?
- Excuse me!
Can I have your attention, please
ladies and gentlemen?
That man, John Acardo
is a drug dealer and killer.
I want you all to remember his face
and the faces of his men here
so that you can describe them
later to the police.
They're gonna physically assault me
or worse...
the moment I walk out that door.
Thank you and good night.
Arrange a dinner tomorrow night.
Il Tavolo Bianco.
My usual table.
Hey. Careful.
Get over here!
"The question isn't what medical
equipment do we supply."
It's what don't we supply.
Gelatin capsules, glass vials
hospital beds
and everything in between.
- Put that in the corner, Bob.
- "Okay."
What about blood-test strips?
Did these come from Rutherford Medical?
Uh, yeah, these are
from our home-typing kits.
Do you also handle the results?
No, this particular strip is from a home kit
so there's no need
to send in for a lab report.
"Bow and arrow.'
- Agent Cho.
- Yeah.
It's a bow and arrow.
The first trafficking victim
that Jane found...
Didn't she say something
about a bow and arrow?
Just before she died.
That's a blood-type kit
from our Arquero line.
That's one of our best sellers.
We're gonna need a printout of everyone
who ordered one of these kits.
That's a long list.
We sell those to half of the hospitals
and clinics in the state.
We'll wait.
Whatever.
Mr. Acardo.
And how is my Bella Donna tonight?
Aurelio, you always make be blush.
Your, uh, usual table is waiting.
- Excellent.
- May I hang your coat?
Of course. And, uh, take
Nico's coat, too, would ya?
Of course.
Marie, show Mr. Acardo
to his table, eh?
Take good care of Mr. Acardo, eh?
Johnny, how do you think
I'd look in a Cartier necklace?
Uh, no need, Alfons.
Um...
I think I'll have
a New York strip tonight...
Rare.
And, uh, salad? Is that good?
A salad for her.
- Yeah.
- Thank you, Alfons.
It's me.
I've got it.
Drop it on the ground.
Now come here.
You know what to do.
Drop the weapon.
Drop it now.
Don't shoot!
I am unarmed.
- Put the gun down!
- Okay. Be calm.
God. Hey.
Fischer. Can you breathe?
I'm okay.
Check the shooter.
- I heard shooting. Everyone all right?
- Oh, yeah.
- He's dead.
- Ah. This is how Acardo orders his hits.
He sends a message through Aurelio
to distance himself from the gunman.
They made me.
They made me do this.
Calm down! Put your hands
on your head.
And then Acardo puts the target's name
in the pocket of the jacket.
Patrick Jane.
That's me.
Excuse me.
I think this, uh, belongs to you.
Sit down and put your hands
on the table.
And this.
- And this.
- Oh, my God! He's choking!
He's choking!
Oh, my God! He's choking!
- Do something! Do something!
- Here we go. Ready?
One, two, three.
There we go, huh?
- All better and off to prison.
- Let's go. Come on.
Oh, God.
Oh, thank you.
Um...
- Choking?
- No, I'm good.
Hey, Jane.
Did you hear the news?
Your grand jury investigation ended.
And they voted to indict you for murder.
- Well, is it any wonder?
- Well, the AG is making it go away
but, you know, it's a good thing
that you're under our protection.
That's a fact
that you'll never let me forget.
How was your dinner with Lisbon?
Oh, my chicken was so-so,
but Lisbon's fish was excellent.
- Why do you ask?
- Just wondering.
Lydia Faulk.
Agent Fischer.
We didn't recall you to testify. I'll let you
know if we need you to come back in.
Oh, that won't be necessary.
The case against Jane was a setup.
- What are you talking about?
- A sting to net a corrupt prosecutor.
You're under arrest
for grand jury tampering and bribery.
- Bailiff, take these people out.
- Arrest warrant. Back off.
We have Acardo's phone.
The two of you had a lot to say
to each other
the night he received his subpoena
to appear before the grand jury.
And then there's the large deposit
into your offshore account two days later.
Cuff her.
Okay, well...
We have good news for you.
The Attorney General agreed not to
prosecute if you testify against Acardo.
Acardo came to me
and said he'd make my wife a widow
if I didn't do what he ordered, eh?
You will be moved
to protective custody, of course.
And what about Il Tavolo Bianco, eh?
I testify for you.
But I won't leave my home
or my restaurant.
If Acardo wants revenge
I'll stay out in the open
where they can find me.
Otherwise, they hurt my family
to find me.
Okay.
Well, you will have to remain
in protective custody until the trial.
I understand.
I'll send an agent in
to walk you through that.
Good luck.
You made a tough choice, Mr. Aurelio.
Brave man.
That's very admirable.
Agent Cho.
What am I looking at?
Uh, I cross-referenced a list of facilities
that purchased the Arquero kits
with their location
and last date of purchase.
- What am I looking at?
- Oh, well, if...
if you'll notice the highlighted line
20 kits were delivered to Wheatondale
Medical Center last month.
- Okay?
- Wheatondale isn't in operation.
It was condemned two years ago.
Let's try the other door.
Let's break it.
You hear that?
That humming sound?
Sounds like a generator.
It's coming from in there.
Someone's been using
this place.
Yeah, but for what?
The hum is coming from in there.
What? What is it?
The body's been cut open.
Looks like they took the heart.
They're killing these girls
for their organs.
Jane.
Lisbon in?
Yeah.
Teresa. It's, uh...
it's Jane.
- What's up?
- Cannoli...
Il Tavolo Bianco.
Mrs. Aurelio made them specially.
- That's sweet.
- Yeah.
There's, there's enough there
for Marcus, too.
Jane. You didn't come here this late
to drop off cannoli.
Look, I-I've been thinking
about you leaving.
And...
I want you to know
that I-I really want you to be happy.
And that is the most important
thing to me...
That you do what makes you happy.
- Okay?
- Yeah.